# Luis Gutierrez

Experienced and driven to grow my knowledge and skillsets. Over the last 10 years I've gained experience with Adobe Photoshop, Video editors, photography, design and now Web Development. As someone who always dabbled with tech, Web Development in the last few months has been something I'm continuously looking to grow my knowledge in. I have learned to work with HTML, CSS and now getting familiarized with JavaScript and WordPress.

24850 Hancock Ave APT. F204 92562 (951)440-8285 lcienfuegos95@gmail.com https://github.com/luisgcodes

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Moreno Valley Unified School District

08/2016 to Present, Moreno Valley, CA

Assisted in the creation of a classroom environment conducive to learning and appropriate to the physical, social and emotional development of students.

#### Winco Foods .Co — Product Stocker

06/2015 to 08/2016, San Jacinto, CA

- · Provided customers with general information
- · Assisted with setup and breakdown of equipment and products received
- Worked at a fast paced

#### **EDUCATION**

# California Baptist University — Liberal Studies

10/2018 to 07/2020

Have worked in the Moreno Valley Unified School District as an instructional Asistant SDS for over 6 years.

## University of California Riverside — Web Development Bootcamp

02/2022 to Present

Experience working with:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Node
- Express
- BootStrap
- Tailwind
- Git